Can't you just do it
online instead?
Mom, I'll be right back.
You better be.
Take care too, Mom.
Joey, let's go?
I don't even know where to start
once we get to Valmora.
I've got it covered,
I know someone there.
- Who?
- Zoey.
Andrew, what brings you here?
I'm swallowing my pride...
I need your help.
Dad? Dad, wait!
Dad!
What's all that noise?
We thought you were cops!
Looks like this pretty one
is lost.
Want us to help you?
Miss, did you see the girl I was
with earlier?
She left,
she went that way.
Come on, let's talk inside.
Let go of me!
Come here, Andrew!
I've got too many enemies,
I can't handle them alone!
Where do you think you're going?
Your luck's running out.
Cops! Let's go!
Joey, this is Zoey.
She'll be helping us
while we're here in Valmora.
I'm his ex-girlfriend
by the way.
I thought Joey was a guy.
Is there a problem
if his friend's a girl?
Depends, how close are you?
- What's that?
- Take a look.
Don't tell me you're giving me
a makeover?
Yes, just follow my advice.
Why did you leave the eatery?
I thought I saw my dad.
I really feel like
he's still alive...
and he's here looking
for Berdugo.
Berdugo?
Now, it's your time.
Yes! Yes!
Faster! Faster!
Sorry, sorry!
No!
Use your shoulder!
I'll show you.
One, two, three, four!
Eight...
nine...
last one!
Whoo!
I've prepared people to go
with you on your trip.
And the cargo?
Berdugo, how are you, my dear?
Delilah, I'm all set
for my trip.
And the samples?
Ready.
These products are topnotch.
You won't be disappointed.
Well, to taste and experience
is to believe.
I'm looking forward
to put a face
to the mysterious Berdugo.
I'll see you soon, my dear.
So your theory is Berdugo
will replace
Godfather as the supplier
here in Valmora?
Seems like it,
that's why I came to you
I know you can use this lead.
You know, Andrew,
you could've told me
all of that over the phone.
Why come here in Valmora?
For Joey?
You're such a kind friend,
and dedicated journalist.
Of course I want to be the first
to expose Berdugo.
Oh, right.
Exposé.
Why isn't it here.
- Joey?
- It's not here.
Wait, what happened?
The keychain my dad gave me,
it's gone.
Maybe you dropped it
when you fought those addicts.
Ah, okay, Joey...
Tomorrow, we'll go back for it
if needed.
Nice one.
No wonder...
you have a great body...
you're really good at abs.
You deserve a reward...
Coffee...
with me?
Ah, pass.
Who is that?
That's confusing.
I didn't say anything wrong.
You know what?
Your tone, your attitude...
You look like a creep!
What? A perv?
No!
She's just picky.
I didn't say anything bad.
What should it be then?
Go on, you.
How?
Watch and learn, okay?
Hello.
But still,
kudos for your effort.
I'm sorry,
but I didn't understand.
But still, thank you.
See?
It's easy.
You're amazing, Oppa but...
what did you say?
I told her her form
is dangerous,
she could injure herself,
and the shoes are not ideal.
That's it?
You shut her down
but she still liked it?
I told you.
It's not what you say.
It's how you say it.
No, no.
I think it's the language.
you just acted like an oppa
and she already got excited.
Unfair! That's so unfair.
So next time, when you see Joey,
you know what to do.
Just remember, posture, form,
eye contact.
Sure you noticed the difference.
I don't know, Oppa.
Do I really need all of this
just for her to notice me?
You're a good guy, Peter.
You will be good for Joey.
She just need to see you
in a different light.
I'll get it, Oppa.
You will figure out
the timing eventually.
And please stop calling me
"oppa."
Oppa is only used by girls.
So what should I call you
instead?
Call me "hyung," okay?
- Hyung?
- Yes, hyung.
Only because we are good,
true friends now.
No, I', not use to this,
I'm used calling you oppa.
- Just Oppa then.
- No, no.
- Hyung.
- No, no. Oppa.
- Hyung! Hyung!
- Oppa!
Oppa.
If you don't,
you will regret it.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Oppa...
Oppa, huh?
You can stay here
as long as you need.
I live alone anyway...
and frankly,
I welcome the company.
Thank you, Zoey.
Once I find my dad,
I won't be a burden anymore.
No problem.
Andrew, can I talk to you?
Just for a bit.
Sure.
Hello?
Joey...
Dad?
Joey, my child...
I knew it.
I never believed
you were dead, Dad.
I felt that you were
still alive.
Who's with you there?
No one.
Don't tell Andrew
that you're talking to me.
How did you know
Andrew's with me?
Dad?
Dad!
I was right!
You're the man
I was following earlier.
But, Dad, how did that happen?
Wasn't your car completely
burned?
How did you get here?
Why didn't you come home to us?
It's a long story, Joey.
When I returned to service,
I felt that...
my life was in danger.
Oh, sorry...
I saw a man outside the station.
He's the same guy
who caused trouble
while Andrew was
interviewing me.
Hey!
And he's also the man
I saw at our house!
At our house?
Okay, Dad, please be careful.
Hey!
Go ahead, chase me.
Leave my family alone!
Is he the man who tried
to kill you?
Yes, Joey.
We fought.
After that, I saw he was
carrying a photo...
A photo of our family.
Don't drag my family into this!
You want to save your family?
Then you'll die!
But I couldn't do anything...
Chief, I need help.
I knew it, Dad.
I had a feeling...
Chief Lansang was hiding
something from me.
That's why he didn't want
to show us your body.
And you know what?
Even Mom, she refuses
to believe it.
She doesn't want to hope
that you're still alive.
Joey, I understand why
your mother feels that way.
Because, Dad, what you did
to us really hurt.
You made us look like fools.
We mourned someone,
who was actually still alive.
You know, you still
haven't changed.
You're still handsome.
Maybe you've matured,
just a little.
Oh.
Well, I am getting older.
It's been...
four years...
since we last saw each other.
I don't think it's age.
Stress.
Well, it's a stressful job.
I really want to get
this exposé.
Is that really what you want?
Are you sure about that?
What else?
Well...
Joey's pretty.
It's not hard to be attracted
to her.
- Maybe you're doing this...
- to help my friend.
That's all there is to it.
So you can honestly say
you don't like her?
Look, ah...
Zoey...
This mission
is my priority right now.
I don't have any other
intention but that...
and to help my friend Joey.
Please don't read
anything else into it.
All right, fine.
I'm just asking.
- Bro.
- Oh.
I'll go ahead.
You're leaving already?
Let's hang out for a bit,
my treat.
Let's have a drink.
It's my way of thanking you
for all the lessons
and the makeover.
I can't.
Why?
Someone waiting for you?
Hey, don't think I forgot.
You still owe me.
You haven't told me
where you've been
or what you've been doing.
I even asked your landlady.
She got mad at me.
You looked for me?
Of course!
I was worried about you.
For all I knew,
you were already dead...
because of some syndicate.
I mean, I didn't realize
that you care for me like that.
Of course, we're friends, right?
Joey said we're solid, right?
You know, if Joey's dad
weren't dead,
I'm sure he'd be looking
for you too.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
that I moved.
You moved?
Where?
Somewhere closer
where Theresa might be.
What?
That's dangerous.
Do you have a death wish
or something?
Don't worry.
I'm being very careful.
I trust you...
Mr. Intelligence Agent.
Just don't disappear again
without telling me,
okay, Oppa?
- It's hyung.
- Oppa.
Hyung.
- Hyung.
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry, Joey,
but this is the only way
to make sure you're safe.
I'm the syndicate's target...
and I know they won't stop
until I'm dead.
It hurts me to lie to you...
but I'm doing all this for you.
But, Dad, what do we do now?
Are you really going
to pretend you're dead?
Dad, does this mean we can't be
with you and Mom anymore?
No, Joey.
I know Berdugo's plan.
I will bring down the syndicate.
After that,
we'll be together again.
Dad, I'll help you.
It's hard to do this alone.
It'll be easier to find Berdugo
if you have someone with you.
Dad, I just don't want anything
bad to happen to you.
Joey, don't.
Just go home.
Stay with your mother.
Tell her you talked to me
and that I'm alive.
But don't text or call me...
so we stay safe.
But, Dad, Andrew is with me
right now,
and we also have an agent
from the DDE.
We can help you.
Joey, don't insist.
No one can know that I'm alive.
It's too dangerous.
Trust is hard...
Even with Andrew?
Okay, fine.
Just make sure you handle
everything in Valmora.
We're counting on you.
Boss, everything's set.
We already have
a local contact there
to make sure your transaction
with Delilah goes smoothly.
Good.
Let's keep these people
on our payroll.
They'll also be our men
once we take over Valmora.
We're close, Boss.
After that, our expansion
continues.
Valmora now...
Soon, the entire Philippines.
Dear, no one must know
that I'm alive.
Don't call this number.
Wait for my call.
Yes, Dad, please be careful.
I love you, Dad.
Joey.
Who were you talking to?
My mom.
There's this woman
on my radar, Delilah.
Looks like Berdugo is meeting
someone here.
It might be her.
Andrew, just stay put.
My plan is to get close to her,
I'll handle it.
So what now?
Are we at a dead end?
I've got an idea.
Since we're already here, right?
I called earlier for a suite.
I didn't expect
to have neighbors.
Let's just follow
Joey and Andrew.
We can help them too.
If this is what I need to do
to help my father,
I'll do it.
What are you doing there?
Just make sure
he doesn't ruin my plan.
Francis, the owner
of this resort.
Everything is ready
for your guests' arrival,
Madam Delilah.
If this deal goes South...
I stand to lose a lot.